The whole point of LinkedIn is to connect to or make a network
领英全部的意义就在于进入或搭建人脉圈
of peers and other professionals for the purpose of collaboration.
结识同辈和其它专业人士、达成合作
Whether this collaboration is based on mutual interest projects, mentorship,
无论合作的基点是互惠互利的项目、导师-学生关系、
extra-curricular activities or job prospects,
业余活动或职业前景
networking is your main task when using LinkedIn.
拓展人脉都是你使用领英的主要任务
The site does a great job of helping you get your network started,
这个网站非常有用 能帮你开始搭建人脉网络
making it grow and providing a constant barrage of new potential contacts.
扩大社交圈并提供源源不断的潜在社交资源
As your network grows,
随着你的社交圈扩大
it will begin to look something like this.
它看起来会像这样
Each time you make a connection,
每结识一个新朋友
you uncover more connections,
你就激活了更多人际关系
which will lead to multiple levels or degrees of contacts.
最终会成为不同级别、不同程度的人脉
LinkedIn labels these levels is first,
领英把它们标注为一级、
second, third degree connections.
二级、三级人脉
First degree connections are the actual connections you have made with people.
一级人脉是你和其它人达成的实实在在的联系
They will be your network.
它们构成你的人际关系网
Second degree connections are people
二级人脉是和你的一级人脉
with whom your first degree connections connected with.
连接起来的人
You can think of second degree connections as friends of friends.
你可以把二级人脉理解为朋友的朋友
Third degree connections, you can guess,
三级人脉 你能猜到的
are connections of second degree connections
就是通过二级人脉连接的人
LinkedIn will show all of these connections and you can connect with,
领英会展示出这所有的联系人
message or interact with any of these connections at anytime.
任何时候你都可以与他们结识 发信息或互动
These individuals can also interact and see you as well.
这些人也可以看到你 与你互动
This interaction between levels is what will allow recruiters to find you.
而跨级互动可以让雇主找到你
However, as this graphic shows,
但是 如图像所示
the more you grow your network,
你的人际圈越扩大 你的简历
the more challenging it becomes to make your profile stand
想引人注目也会变得越有挑战
out because you're being connected to an exponential number of connections.
因为你的联系人数目已经有了指数级增长
That said, the first five elements of your profile are
虽然如此 简历的首要五因素
the make or break for grabbing attention and selling to a recruiter,
依然是成败关键 决定你是否能获得注意
colleague, friend or anyone on taking more time to look into your profile in more detail.
吸引雇主、同事、朋友花更多时间更细致地阅读你简历
You aren't trying to sell yourself in two,
你不是要在两秒、三秒、
three or four seconds,
四秒内推销自己
you just need to get them to click on
你只需要让他们点击你的简历
your profile so they can get the rest of your story.
这样他们可以了解完整的你
One of our curriculum leads here at Udacity even got
我们优达的一位课程主管 甚至
her job by old colleague of hers posting it on LinkedIn,
是通过她的前同事放在领英上的信息找到了工作
even though it wasn't advertised anywhere else.
虽然这条工作信息在其它任何地方都没有发布
There are a few tactics you can use to expand your professional network.
你可以用一些小技巧来扩大职业人脉
Connecting to organizations such as
与一些组织如优达校友圈
Udacity Alumni Network or a specific nano-degree program LinkedIn group,
或某个纳米学位的领英群建立联系
such as Udacity VR Developer Nano-Degree can quickly boost your network into new areas.
如优达 VR 开发者纳米学位群 能迅速把你的人脉扩展到新领域
Examine second and third degree connections.
查看了解二级和三级人脉
Find connections that can apply to and assist you in your network expansion.
找到那些能用于或帮助你扩大社交圈的联系人
Investigate companies you'd like to work for or are in your targeted interest area.
调查那些你想为之工作或在你兴趣领域内的公司
Find the recruiters and cold call them.
找到他们负责招聘的人并主动打电话给他们
Using cold calls in LinkedIn is simply sending these new people
用领英的联系方式给这些人打破冰电话
a connection invite with a message declaring your interest in them,
能在你们之间建立联系 传递的信息是
their company, their field, et cetera.
你对他们的公司、领域等感兴趣
Be polite, respectful and direct.
态度要礼貌、尊重、直接
Ask for informative interviews or who you can connect
询问公司有无招聘宣讲或可以联系谁
with in order to get information or job opportunities.
获得信息和招聘机会
People like being needed.
人们喜欢被需要
Use these techniques and make those connections.
用这些技巧发掘上述的人脉 例如, 我想在深度学习领域开启职业生涯
I find a second degree connection that works at
我找到一个二级人脉 他在一家
a large software developing company in their deep learning department.
大型软件开发公司的深度学习部门工作
I would send them a connection request with a message like "Hi.
我会向他们发送好友请求 备注信息可以是
My name is Matt. I'm currently trying to change
“你好 我叫 Matt 我现在正努力转行
careers into the software industry, specifically deep learning.
进入软件行业, 尤其是深度学习行业
I would love to connect with you and discuss any advice you
能否加我好友并且给我一些建议
may have to make this transition a reality.
帮助我顺利转行
Hope to hear from you soon."
期待很快得到你的回复 "
This is one way to make use of your connections to get info on positions,
这是利用人脉获得职位信息、所需技能、
required skills, new contacts among other vital networking information.
新的人脉等其他关键社交信息的方法
In all of our research into this topic here at Udacity,
在优达探讨这个话题所有的探讨中
we have found that the number one boost to
我们发现对找工作帮助最大的
your job search is your network and networking skills.
就是你的人脉和拓展人脉的技巧
In fact, there are many more jobs only available through
事实上 只能通过社交圈获得的职位数量
networking than there are advertised on job posting sites.
要多于发布在求职网站上的职位数量